Alexander Glover

Gooseberry Hill, Western Australia 6076 | 0438725598 | alexk.glover@gmail.com | Pfizer Vaccinated

Summary and Objective

I am an experienced student and employee in different fields of the work force and have developed many skills such as, independence and reliability as well as critical thinking, problem solving and adaptability to a variety of work environments. Through playing hockey, I have developed teamwork, communication skills and socials skills. While participating/competing in Muay Thai I have developed my confidence, perseverance and responsibility. And through my own study and time I have developed basics of programming in SQL and Python through Code Academy and other resources.

My objective in applying for employment with a company is to gain experience and skills in the related working environment associated with my studies at university. Ideally, I would like a working position that would allow time for my university studies and afternoon/nightly curricular activities.

Achievements

- Kairos; Religious and self-development retreat 2017
- Singapore Hockey Tour 2017
- Received MVP award for Curtin Trinity Pirates Hockey Club Division 4 2020, 2021
- Achieved Blue Singlet in Muay Thai 2021
- Captain of the Murdoch Esports Dota 2 Team 2021
- Codecademy Completed SQL Basic Course 2021
- Codecademy Completed Python3 Basic Course 2021

Skills

- Computer skills
- Good listening skills
- Cultural awareness
- Teamwork
- Critical thinking
- Computer proficiency
- Responsible
- Organization and Time management
- Reading comprehension
- Flexible & Adaptable
- Problem Solving
- MS Office
- Understanding and skills in the programming languages SQL and Python3 through Codecademy (certificates attached)

Work History

Labourer: New Age Carpentry | 2019 – Current

- Used critical thinking to break down problems, evaluate solutions and make decisions.
- Improved operations through consistent hard work and dedication.

- Successfully maintain clean, valid driver's license and access to reliable transportation.
- Demonstrated respect, friendliness and willingness to help wherever needed.
- Quickly learned new skills and applied them to daily tasks, improving efficiency and productivity.
- Worked closely with manager to provide effective assistance for specific aspects of business operation.
- Lifted and carried heavy materials.
- Followed established job site safety regulations and maintained safe and clean work area.
- Followed protocols and stayed organized to provide personal and teammate safety.
- Shaped or cut materials to specified measurements using hand tools, machines and power saws.

Kitchen Hand: Embers Restaurant and Pizzeria | 2016 – Current

- Compiled recipe ingredients and prepared for cooks by washing, cutting or measuring food items
- Restocked supplies and prepared additional ingredients during downtime for expected busy periods.
- Circulated kitchen area to receive work assignments and identify support tasks.
- Sanitized dining ware and kitchen equipment according to health code standards.
- Learned other teammates' work tasks to train as backup.
- Cleaned and sanitized dishes and utensils, consistently keeping adequate supplies on hand for expected customer loads.
- Maintained high personal grooming standards and uniform presentation.
- Maintained composure and work quality while under stress.
- Sanitized pots, pans, utensils, kitchen appliances and equipment using company-approved cleaning supplies.

Education

Mazenod College - Lesmurdie, WA

High School Diploma

Graduated: 2017

Murdoch University - Perth, WA

Studying: Business Information and Databases | 2019 – current

Completed Units:

ICT170: Foundations of Computer Systems

Topics include digital logic, memory, storage, processing paradigms, operating systems, programming languages, systems development, deployment and professional ethics

ICT169: Foundations of Data Communications

Practical exercises with switches and routers will place the theory in context, allowing students to design, build and troubleshoot networks.

ICT158: Introduction of Information Systems

Provides a balance of technical and organisational perspectives to serve as the basis for further study in the discipline.

MAS162: Foundations of Discrete Mathematics

The learning approach is very much problem based using a combination of theoretical and computational viewpoints to investigate and explore the unit material.

ICT284: Systems Analysis and Design

Methods and techniques for analysing problematic organisational situations, particularly those leading to the development of an information system and draws on both technical and organisational material to provide the knowledge and skills necessary to design and implement an operational system.

BSC203: Introduction to ICT Research Methods

Introduction to research in the information and communications technology (ICT) discipline.

Hobbies

- Field Hockey
- Indoor Hockey
- Muay Thai
- Netball
- Programming
- Gym
- Reading
- Gaming

References

- Dominica Ferrari (Manager at Embers Restaurant); Ph: + 04 28 938 467; email: acounts@emberswoodfired.com (email preferred method of contact due to busy schedule)
- Scott Broadhurst (Builder for New Age Carpentry); Ph: +04 39 932 707; email: scott@newagecarpentry.com.au